Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
الموقع الرسمي: kissasian.be ترجمة =Qari= @Team Viki
[This drama is fictional, and any resemblance to real people or events is coincidental.]
[هذه الدراما خيالية، وأي تشابه مع أشخاص أو أحداث حقيقية هو محض مصادفة.]
[Episode 7]
[الحلقة 7]
If Kim Yeong Ran doesn't show up immediately,
إذا لم يظهر كيم يونج ران على الفور،
I can't guarantee her mother's life.
لا أستطيع ضمان حياة والدتها.
I'm the late Chairman Ga Sung Ho's lawyer.
أنا محامي الرئيس الراحل جا سونغ هو.
I'm not her mother's lawyer.
أنا لست محامي والدتها.
Do whatever you want.
افعل ما تريد.
[Ms. Bu Se Mi]
[السيدة بو سي مي]
[Gaseong Art Center]
[مركز غاسيونغ للفنون]
Save me.
أنقذني.
Your daughter takes after you, cold-hearted.
ابنتك تشبهك ، بقلب بارد.
Says she doesn't care whether her mother lives or dies.
تقول إنها لا تهتم سواء كانت والدتها تعيش أو تموت.
I'll do anything.
سأفعل أي شيء.
Just please save me.
فقط من فضلك أنقذني.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Anything?
أي شئ؟
Yes, I mean it.
نعم، أعني ذلك.
Then
ثم
can you kill your own daughter too?
هل تستطيع أن تقتل ابنتك أيضاً؟
Where is this place?
أين هذا المكان؟
What's this?
ما هذا؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Where am I?
أين أنا؟
Hey! What's this?
مهلا! ما هذا؟
What's this?
ما هذا؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Hey!
يا!
Honey, untie this for me.
عزيزتي، افتحي هذا من أجلي.
Honey!
عسل!
Seon Yeong, Seon Woo!
سون يونغ، سون وو!
Mom, why is Dad here?
أمي لماذا أبي هنا؟
You two, watch carefully.
أنتما الاثنان، انظرا بعناية.
This is what happens when you don't listen to Mom.
هذا ما يحدث عندما لا تستمع إلى أمي.
Seon Yeong.
سيون يونغ.
Save me.
أنقذني.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
What's going on!
ماذا يحدث هنا!
Hey!
يا!
Jeon Dong Min?
جون دونغ مين؟
Hey, catch.
مهلا، امسك.
You want me to drive?
هل تريدني أن أقود؟
Yeah, I've been feeling stiff lately,
نعم، لقد كنت أشعر بالتيبس في الآونة الأخيرة،
so I thought I'd jog to the greenhouse for exercise.
لذلك اعتقدت أنني سأذهب إلى الدفيئة لممارسة الرياضة.
Take the car and come.
خذ السيارة وتعالى.
Oh, you're copying Ms. Bu Se Mi now?
أوه، هل تنسخ الآنسة بو سي مي الآن؟
Are you following me?
هل تتبعني؟
No.
لا.
I'm just on my way to the greenhouse.
أنا فقط في طريقي إلى الدفيئة.
Is your hand okay?
هل يدك بخير؟
Oh, this?
أوه هذا؟
It's nothing serious.
ليس هناك شيء خطير.
It feels great to run like this in the morning after so long, right?
من الرائع أن أركض بهذه الطريقة في الصباح بعد كل هذا الوقت، أليس كذلك؟
The air is refreshing too.
الهواء منعش أيضاً
Running together is better than alone, right?
الركض معًا أفضل من الركض بمفردك، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
By the way, Mr. Jeon.
بالمناسبة، السيد جيون.
Yes?
نعم؟
We already passed your greenhouse.
لقد مررنا بالفعل بالبيت الزجاجي الخاص بك.
Ah.
اه.
Oh, I usually drive, that's why.
أوه، أنا عادة أقود السيارة، هذا هو السبب.
I'll go ahead first.
سأذهب للأمام أولاً.
See you at home later.
أراك في المنزل لاحقًا.
I'm really not like what I used to be anymore.
أنا حقا لم أعد كما كنت من قبل.
Ms. Bu, you're working out again today.
السيدة بو، أنت تتدربين مرة أخرى اليوم.
Oh, have you seen Dong Min?
أوه، هل رأيت دونغ مين؟
Oh, Mr. Jeon went that way earlier.
أوه، السيد جيون ذهب بهذه الطريقة في وقت سابق.
Why that way?
لماذا بهذه الطريقة؟
He suddenly decided to start working out this morning, made such a fuss about it.
قرر فجأة أن يبدأ في ممارسة التمارين الرياضية هذا الصباح، وأثار ضجة كبيرة حول هذا الأمر.
By the way, Miss, well...
بالمناسبة، يا آنسة، حسنًا...
What kind of guys does Hye Ji like?
ما نوع الرجال الذي تحبه هيه جي؟
Ask her directly.
اسألها مباشرة.
But I'm too shy to ask her myself.
ولكنني خجول جدًا بحيث لا أستطيع أن أسألها بنفسي.
Tae Min, Tae Min.
تاي مين، تاي مين.
Bu Se Mi.
بو سي مي.
You.
أنت.
Someone's coming.
شخص ما قادم.
Be careful.
احرص.
Pardon?
عفو؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
You have a visitor.
لديك زائر.
Visitor?
زائر؟
Who?
من؟
It's been a while, Vice President.
لقد مر وقت طويل، نائب الرئيس.
Lee Don.
لي دون.
How did you find this place?
كيف وجدت هذا المكان؟
It was you, right?
لقد كنت أنت، أليس كذلك؟
You're the one who put me in here?
أنت الذي وضعني هنا؟
Let's talk nicely, please.
دعونا نتحدث بشكل لطيف من فضلك.
I'm a believer in non-violence.
أنا أؤمن باللاعنف.
Let go of me!
أتركني!
It took some work to find this place.
لقد استغرق الأمر بعض العمل للعثور على هذا المكان.
She hid you away quite thoroughly.
لقد أخفتك تمامًا.
What nonsense is this?
ما هذا الهراء؟
Doesn't this place
أليس هذا المكان
feel familiar to you?
هل تشعر بالألفة معك؟
No way.
مستحيل.
Did my sister really do this?
هل أختي فعلت هذا حقا؟
You were going to sell the company, which is like her life, to Chinese investors.
كنت تنوي بيع الشركة، التي هي بمثابة حياتها، إلى مستثمرين صينيين.
Do you really think Professor Ga would let that pass
هل تعتقد حقًا أن البروفيسور جا سيسمح بذلك؟
just because you are her brother?
فقط لأنك شقيقها؟
So, what do you want to say?
إذن ماذا تريد أن تقول؟
I'll get you out of this hospital immediately,
سأخرجك من هذا المستشفى على الفور،
restore your damaged reputation,
استعادة سمعتك المتضررة،
and make you CEO of Gaseong Group.
وجعلك الرئيس التنفيذي لمجموعة Gaseong.
Vice President.
نائب الرئيس.
Shall we join forces?
هل يجب علينا أن نجمع قوانا؟
Forces?
القوات؟
Are you insane?
هل انت مجنون؟
[Hospital Admission Form]
[نموذج قبول المستشفى]
[Guardian: Ga Seon Yeong]
[الوصي: جا سيون يونغ]
This...
هذا...
Is my sister really doing this to me?
هل أختي تفعل هذا بي حقا؟
This.
هذا.
Is my own sister really doing this? Huh?
هل أختي تفعل هذا حقًا؟ هاه؟
You have no parents,
ليس لديك والدين
no spouse,
لا يوجد زوج
and Professor Ga is your only guardian.
والأستاذ جا هو الوصي الوحيد عليك.
You know you can't discharge yourself without a guardian, right?
أنت تعلم أنك لا تستطيع أن تخرج نفسك بدون ولي أمر، أليس كذلك؟
How could my sister do this to me?
كيف يمكن لأختي أن تفعل بي هذا؟
How could she!
كيف لها ذلك؟
I know everything.
انا اعرف كل شئ
I know what she did.
أنا أعلم ماذا فعلت.
Hey, Attorney Lee.
مرحبًا، المحامي لي.
Do you know any reporters?
هل تعرف أي صحفيين؟
I'm going to blow everything wide open.
سأفجر كل شيء على مصراعيه.
Vice President.
نائب الرئيس.
Mind if I hear that story too?
هل تمانع أن أسمع هذه القصة أيضًا؟
Actually, I might be able to get you out of here for sure.
في الواقع، ربما أكون قادرًا على إخراجك من هنا بالتأكيد.
Hey.
يا.
Do you think I'm stupid?
هل تعتقد أنني غبي؟
Why would I believe a word you say?
لماذا أصدق كلمة تقولها؟
Then there's nothing more to say.
إذن لا يوجد شيء آخر ليقال.
As Chairman Ga Sung Ho's lawyer,
بصفته محامي الرئيس جا سونغ هو،
I've shown enough goodwill.
لقد أظهرت ما يكفي من حسن النية.
I'll take my leave now.
سوف آخذ إجازتي الآن.
Go back inside.
ارجع إلى الداخل.
What should we play in the Strawberry Class?
ماذا يجب أن نلعب في فئة الفراولة؟
Let's run a hundred laps together.
دعونا نجري مائة لفة معًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Look what they're doing.
انظر ماذا يفعلون
- Hello.
- مرحبا.
Miss, come here for a second.
آنسة، تعالي هنا لثانية واحدة.
Strawberry Class kids, stay inside.
أطفال صف الفراولة، ابقوا في الداخل.
- Okay.
-حسنًا.
Miss, can I ask you a favor?
آنسة، هل يمكنني أن أطلب منك معروفًا؟
No, you may not.
لا، لا يجوز لك ذلك.
No, absolutely not.
لا، بالتأكيد لا.
Principal, what's wrong?
مدير المدرسة، ما المشكلة؟
Today's parent observation day, right?
اليوم هو يوم مراقبة الوالدين، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
All the parents are dying to see a class taught
جميع الآباء يتوقون لرؤية فصل دراسي يتم تدريسه
by an Iseon Women's University graduate.
من قبل خريجة جامعة إيسيون للسيدات.
What should we do, Miss?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل يا آنسة؟
Would you like to give a class today?
هل ترغب في إعطاء درس اليوم؟
Oh, please.
أوه، من فضلك.
You said you'd handle all observation classes alone.
لقد قلت أنك ستتعامل مع جميع فصول المراقبة وحدك.
Told us to stay quiet and not teach.
طلب منا أن نبقى هادئين ولا نعلم.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Yes, yes, I did say that.
نعم، نعم، لقد قلت ذلك.
However.
لكن.
[The Sun and Moon Siblings]
[الأخوة الشمس والقمر]
Today I, as principal,
اليوم أنا، كمدير،
will specially permit Ms. Bu Se Mi's class.
سأسمح بشكل خاص لفئة السيدة بو سي مي.
Now, take this.
الآن، خذ هذا.
Nod, just nod.
أومئ، فقط أومئ.
You can do it.
يمكنك فعل ذلك.
Principal.
رئيسي.
Shall I go ahead with the ballet class then?
هل أستمر في درس الباليه إذن؟
I can do it!
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك!
Everyone, today we'll learn about 'plié'.
أيها الجميع، اليوم سوف نتعلم عن لعبة 'Plie'.
Now, let's try following along.
الآن، دعونا نحاول أن نتابع.
First, spread your legs like... no,
أولاً، افرد ساقيك مثل... لا،
spread your feet,
افرد قدميك
hands together in front.
اليدين معًا في الأمام.
Plié.
مطوية.
Good job.
أحسنت.
Now stand back up
الآن قف مرة أخرى
and plié.
ومطوية.
Excellent.
ممتاز.
Ah, moms,
أوه أمي
please massage this part.
من فضلك قم بتدليك هذا الجزء.
It's also great for blood circulation.
كما أنه مفيد جدًا للدورة الدموية.
Now, I'll take a photo of each of you one by one.
الآن، سألتقط صورة لكل واحد منكم واحدًا تلو الآخر.
Let's see who's doing well.
دعونا نرى من يقوم بعمل جيد.
Who wants to go first?
من يريد الذهاب أولا؟
Okay, plié.
حسنًا، مطوية.
Oh, very good.
أوه، جيد جدًا.
So fast, thank you.
سريع جداً، شكرا لك.
Next one, plié.
التالي، مطوي.
Ooh, excellent.
أوه، ممتاز.
Now, we're going to try
الآن سوف نحاول
a de... Demi-plié.
لديه... نصف مطوي.
Ready?
مستعد؟
After the plié here,
بعد الانحناء هنا،
raise your arms sideways.
ارفع ذراعيك إلى الجانبين.
Now, stretch out your arm.
الآن، قم بمد ذراعك.
Let's see whose armpits look nicest!
دعونا نرى من هي صاحبة الإبطين التي تبدو أجمل!
Oh, lovely.
أوه، جميل.
Wow, so beautiful.
واو، جميلة جدًا.
Oh, well done.
أوه، أحسنت.
'Long, long ago, when tigers used to smoke.'
"منذ زمن طويل، عندما كان النمور يدخنون."
'In a small hut deep in the mountains.'
"في كوخ صغير في أعماق الجبال."
'A widowed mother lived there, raising her two young children alone.'
'كانت تعيش هناك أم أرملة، تربي طفليها الصغيرين بمفردها.'
'Every time she went to work, she warned her children.'
'في كل مرة ذهبت إلى العمل، حذرت أطفالها.'
'Kids, when Mommy's not home, never open the door for anyone.'
"أيها الأطفال، عندما لا تكون أمهم في المنزل، لا تفتحوا الباب لأي شخص أبدًا."
'One day, their mother did chores at a village feast.'
'في أحد الأيام، كانت والدتهم تؤدي بعض الأعمال المنزلية في أحد أعياد القرية.'
'She received rice cakes as payment.'
"لقد حصلت على كعك الأرز كدفعة."
'Thinking of her children, she hurried home.'
"كانت تفكر في أطفالها، فعادت مسرعة إلى المنزل."
'I need to give these cakes to my babies quickly.'
"أحتاج إلى إعطاء هذه الكعكات لأطفالي بسرعة."
'But on the shadowy mountain path, there was a tiger as big as a house!'
"ولكن على طريق الجبل المظلل، كان هناك نمر بحجم المنزل!"
'The tiger growled, raising its massive paws.'
"زأر النمر، ورفع مخالبه الضخمة."
'Give me a rice cake, and I won't eat you.'
"أعطني كعكة أرز، ولن آكلك."
'Grrr!'
'غررر!'
'Trembling, the mother handed over the rice cake.'
' سلمت الأم كعكة الأرز وهي ترتجف .'
'The tiger ate the cake and slunk away.'
"أكل النمر الكعكة وهرب."
'Phew.'
'فو.'
'As the mother calmed her racing heart and crossed the next hill, '
"بينما هدأت الأم قلبها المتسارع وعبرت التل التالي،"
'the tiger reappeared, baring its sharp teeth.'
"ظهر النمر مرة أخرى، كاشفًا عن أنيابه الحادة."
'Grrr!'
'غررر!'
'Give me a rice cake, and I won't eat you.'
"أعطني كعكة أرز، ولن آكلك."
'The sister became the sun, and the brother became the moon.'
'أصبحت الأخت الشمس، وأصبح الأخ القمر.'
'They lived happily ever after.'
"لقد عاشوا في سعادة دائمة."
Strawberry Class, everyone.
صف الفراولة، الجميع.
- Yes.
- نعم.
If you're home alone and a stranger asks to open the door,
إذا كنت في المنزل بمفردك وطلب منك شخص غريب فتح الباب،
what should you do?
ماذا يجب عليك أن تفعل؟
- No. - Never let anyone in.
- لا. - لا تدع أحداً يدخل أبداً.
- I must never open the door. - No.
- لا يجب علي أن أفتح الباب أبدًا. - لا.
Never ever.
أبدا أبدا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
This is Iseon Kindergarten's unique interactive class!
هذه هي الفئة التفاعلية الفريدة من نوعها في روضة إيسيون !
Strawberry Class.
صف الفراولة.
One, two, three!
واحد اثنين ثلاثة!
- Grrr!
- غررر!
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
That was great, Miss.
كان ذلك عظيما، يا آنسة.
Sorry to interrupt.
عذرا على المقاطعة.
Ms. Bu Se Mi.
السيدة بو سي مي.
Yes?
نعم؟
Daughter! My daughter!
ابنتي! ابنتي!
Parents,
آباء،
our next class is physical education.
درسنا القادم هو التربية البدنية.
Please follow us to the Apple Classroom with your children.
من فضلك اتبعنا إلى Apple Classroom مع أطفالك.
Strawberry Class, move out!
فصل الفراولة، تحركوا!
- Move out.
- اخرج.
Let's all do the pliés we learned earlier as we go out.
دعونا جميعًا نؤدي الحركات التي تعلمناها سابقًا أثناء خروجنا.
- Plié.
- مطوي.
Plié.
مطوية.
Didn't you miss me?
ألم تفتقدني؟
Yeong Ran.
يونغ ران.
Do you know how hard it was for Mommy to come here?
هل تعلم كم كان الأمر صعبًا على أمي أن تأتي إلى هنا؟
Whoa!
واو!
Yeong Ran.
يونغ ران.
Shouldn't you worry about me coming all this way like this?
ألا يجب عليك أن تقلق بشأن قدومي كل هذه المسافة مثل هذا؟
Is that how I raised you, Yeong Ran?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي ربيتك بها، يونغ ران؟
Why are you rolling your eyes?
لماذا تدحرج عينيك؟
Well, you are Madam now...
حسنًا، أنت سيدتي الآن...
Did Ga Seon Yeong send you?
هل أرسلك جا سون يونغ؟
How did you even get here? Huh?
كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟ هاه؟
See this? This?
انظر هذا؟ هذا؟
That witch Ga Seon Yeong did this to me.
تلك الساحرة جا سون يونغ فعلت هذا بي.
I thought I was going to die.
اعتقدت أنني سأموت.
I ran out without even having time to dress properly.
لقد خرجت دون أن أجد الوقت لارتداء ملابسي بشكل صحيح.
Ugh, this might leave a scar.
أوه، هذا قد يترك ندبة.
How did you find out I was here? Huh?
كيف عرفت أنني هنا؟ هاه؟
Yeong Ran.
يونغ ران.
Only the back of your head was in the article,
فقط الجزء الخلفي من رأسك كان في المقال،
but I recognized you.
ولكنني تعرفت عليك.
Hey.
يا.
Turns out I have maternal instincts too.
يبدو أن لدي غرائز أمومية أيضًا.
So I decided,
لذلك قررت،
I deserve payback for raising you.
أنا أستحق المكافأة لتربيتك.
As payment, ever since I became an adult
كدفعة، منذ أن أصبحت بالغًا
I've been living to pay off your debts day by day, haven't I?
لقد كنت أعيش لسداد ديونك يومًا بعد يوم، أليس كذلك؟
Isn't that enough?
أليس هذا كافيا؟
Thanks to that, you married a man old enough to be your grandfather.
وبفضل ذلك، تزوجت من رجل في سن جدك.
I raised you that way,
لقد ربيتك بهذه الطريقة
tough,
قاسٍ،
so you'd survive anywhere.
حتى تتمكن من البقاء على قيد الحياة في أي مكان.
Your survival skills are all thanks to me.
مهاراتك في البقاء على قيد الحياة كلها بفضلي.
Ugh, I stink.
آه، أنا كريه الرائحة.
I need a warm shower.
أحتاج إلى دش دافئ.
What shower?
أي دش؟
Leave now.
إرحل الآن.
By the way, Yeong Ran,
بالمناسبة، يونغ ران،
be honest.
كن صادقا.
Why did you marry that old man from Gaseong Group?
لماذا تزوجتي ذلك الرجل العجوز من مجموعة غاسونغ؟
Even if you had nothing,
حتى لو لم يكن لديك شيئا،
it doesn't seem like you simply married a man 40 years older than you.
لا يبدو الأمر وكأنك تزوجت من رجل يكبرك بأربعين عامًا.
Did you get something in return?
هل حصلت على شيء في المقابل؟
Or...
أو...
Did you tell that old man to kill himself?
هل طلبت من ذلك الرجل العجوز أن يقتل نفسه؟
Is that something a mother should say to her daughter?
هل هذا شيء ينبغي للأم أن تقوله لابنتها؟
I need to wash up.
أحتاج إلى أن أغتسل.
Any cafes here?
هل يوجد أي مقاهي هنا؟
After my shower, I need to down an iced Americano.
بعد الاستحمام، أحتاج إلى شرب كوب من القهوة الأمريكية المثلجة.
You want to see me?
هل تريد رؤيتي؟
- Secretary Han. - Yes, Professor.
- السكرتير هان. - نعم، أستاذ.
Even if we sway the whole board, to be sure,
حتى لو تمكنا من التأثير على المجلس بأكمله، فمن المؤكد،
we need Seon Woo's shares.
نحن بحاجة إلى أسهم سون وو.
Find Seon Woo by any means necessary.
ابحث عن سون وو بأي وسيلة ضرورية.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Mr. Jeon Dong Min.
السيد جون دونغ مين.
Mr. Jeon Dong Min?
السيد جون دونغ مين؟
Miss.
يفتقد.
Oh, Ju Won.
أوه، جو وون.
Where's your dad?
أين والدك؟
He went to the village chief's house.
ذهب إلى بيت رئيس القرية.
Okay, got it.
حسنًا، حصلت عليه.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك.
Here.
هنا.
This is my favorite candy.
هذه هي الحلوى المفضلة لدي.
When I'm feeling down, this makes me happy.
عندما أشعر بالاكتئاب، هذا يجعلني سعيدًا.
You should try some.
ينبغي عليك أن تجرب بعضًا منها.
How did you know I was in a bad mood?
كيف عرفت أني في مزاج سيء؟
Your mom showed up.
لقد ظهرت والدتك.
I miss my mom too.
أنا أفتقد أمي أيضًا.
But I might get angry if I see her.
ولكنني قد أغضب إذا رأيتها.
She left me and my dad.
لقد تركتني وأبي.
I totally understand how you feel.
أنا أفهم تماما كيف تشعر.
Ju Won.
إنهم أفضل.
If one day I suddenly disappear,
إذا اختفيت فجأة في يوم من الأيام،
would you be angry then too?
هل ستغضب حينها أيضًا؟
Miss.
يفتقد.
If you ever do go somewhere,
إذا ذهبت إلى مكان ما في أي وقت،
promise you'll tell me, okay?
أعدني بأنك ستخبرني، حسنًا؟
Okay.
تمام.
Huh? Where are my slippers?
هاه؟ أين نعالي؟
Why is she wearing them?
لماذا ترتديها؟
Friend, I'll just take three bills today...
صديقي، سأأخذ ثلاث فواتير فقط اليوم...
Wait, I'll only take four.
انتظر، سأأخذ أربعة فقط.
Caught you, thief!
لقد ألقي القبض عليك أيها اللص!
I'm not a thief, old lady.
أنا لست لصًا، يا سيدتي العجوز.
This is what we call catching someone in the act, you thief!
هذا ما نسميه القبض على شخص متلبسًا بالجريمة، أيها اللص!
And I'm not an old lady.
وأنا لست سيدة عجوز.
But you are an old lady.
ولكنك سيدة عجوز.
You liar!
يا كاذب!
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Nyah.
رفض.
Where are you running off to?
إلى أين تهرب؟
Ow! You're stretching my clothes.
آه! أنت تمدد ملابسي.
- Give me the money and go. - No.
- أعطني المال واذهب. - لا.
It's not yours.
إنها ليست لك.
You're so noisy.
أنت صاخبة جدًا.
Oh, Yeong Ran. (Watch on www.kisskh.ws to support Admin)
أوه، يونغ ران. (شاهد على www.kisskh.ws لدعم الإدارة)
My friend.
صديقي.
That woman isn't really your mom, right?
هذه المرأة ليست أمك حقًا، أليس كذلك؟
She's too suspicious.
إنها مشبوهة للغاية.
A friend?
صديق؟
Since when do you call someone who steals other people's money a friend?
منذ متى أصبحت تعتبر من يسرق أموال الآخرين صديقًا؟
Yeong Ran, it's not like that
يونغ ران، الأمر ليس كذلك
- I was... - Ms. Baek Hye Ji.
- كنت... - السيدة بايك هيه جي.
I need to talk to my mom alone.
أريد أن أتحدث مع أمي على انفراد.
Could you step out for a minute?
هل بإمكانك الخروج لمدة دقيقة؟
Is she really your mom? That woman?
هل هي حقا أمك؟ تلك المرأة؟
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
Yeong Ran.
يونغ ران.
I was going to pay it all back with my savings.
كنت سأسدد كل هذا من مدخراتي.
Fine.
بخير.
And don't wear my slippers!
ولا تلبس نعالي!
Yeong Ran.
يونغ ران.
I like it here.
أعجبني هنا.
I want us to live in the same room for a while,
أريد أن نعيش في نفس الغرفة لفترة من الوقت،
patch up the mother-daughter love we couldn't build.
إصلاح حب الأم وابنتها الذي لم نتمكن من بنائه.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You don't have my number.
ليس لديك رقمي.
I'm trying to save it for you.
أحاول أن أحفظه لك.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Type it in.
اكتبها.
Here.
هنا.
By the way, Yeong Ran.
بالمناسبة، يونغ ران.
Did Chairman Ga Sung Ho really commit suicide?
هل انتحر الرئيس جا سونغ هو حقا؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Why don't you guess, Mom?
لماذا لا تخمنين يا أمي؟
Ms. Bu Se Mi!
السيدة بو سي مي!
Who's that?
من هو الذي؟
You have so many questions, Mom.
لديك الكثير من الأسئلة يا أمي.
Don't think about going anywhere, and stay right here.
لا تفكر بالذهاب إلى أي مكان، وابق هنا.
Jeez, which side do I have to pick to make money?
يا إلهي، أي جانب يجب أن أختار لكسب المال؟
Why are you empty-handed?
لماذا أنت فارغ اليدين؟
Weren't you going to give Hae Na a present?
ألم تكن تنوي إعطاء هاى نا هدية؟
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
Dad, wait.
أبي انتظر.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Did you come here to ask me that?
هل أتيت إلى هنا لتسألني ذلك؟
Do you need anything?
هل تحتاج إلى أي شيء؟
Ju Won wanted to play with Hae Na, so I'm going to drop him off.
أراد جو وون اللعب مع هاي نا، لذلك سأتركه.
And for your mother...
ولأمك...
If she needs anything, I'll get it for her.
إذا احتاجت إلى أي شيء، سأحضره لها.
It seems like she came here in a hurry.
يبدو أنها جاءت إلى هنا على عجل.
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
Just call me if you need anything later.
فقط اتصل بي إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء لاحقًا.
Okay.
تمام.
[Psychopath]
[مختل عقليا]
You never know who'll become the cash cow.
لا تعرف أبدًا من سيصبح البقرة الحلوب.
[Kim So Yeong]
[كيم سو يونغ]
What's her real intention here?
ما هي نيتها الحقيقية هنا؟
How did she find out where I am?
كيف عرفت أين أنا؟
What? My phone's already dead.
ماذا؟ هاتفي ميت بالفعل.
Yeong Ran.
يونغ ران.
Where's your phone charger?
أين شاحن هاتفك؟
I lost mine too. We need to buy new ones.
لقد فقدت هاتفي أيضًا. نحتاج لشراء هاتف جديد.
Mom, do you want to go to the local store?
أمي هل تريدين الذهاب إلى المتجر المحلي؟
You seem to need a lot of things.
يبدو أنك بحاجة إلى الكثير من الأشياء.
Earlier, you told me not to move and stay put here.
لقد طلبت مني في وقت سابق عدم التحرك والبقاء هنا.
Take money from that suitcase whenever you need it.
خذ المال من تلك الحقيبة عندما تحتاج إليه.
Yeong Ran.
يونغ ران.
What are you up to now?
ماذا تفعل الآن؟
This is the price for keeping secrets.
هذا هو ثمن الحفاظ على الأسرار.
People here call me Bu Se Mi, not Kim Yeong Ran.
الناس هنا ينادونني بو سي مي، وليس كيم يونج ران.
Bu Se Mi?
بو سي مي؟
Yes, a graduate from Iseon Women's University's Early Childhood Education department.
نعم، خريجة قسم تعليم الطفولة المبكرة بجامعة إيسيون النسائية.
Born in 1994. Raised in Gangnam.
مواليد عام 1994. نشأ في جانجنام.
Father's a professor. Mother runs an art gallery.
أبي أستاذ جامعي، وأمي تدير معرضًا فنيًا.
That's who I need to be for now.
هذا هو الشخص الذي أحتاج أن أكونه الآن.
You know me better than anyone.
أنت تعرفني أفضل من أي شخص آخر.
For that kind of money...
لهذا النوع من المال...
You'd even drink lye if you have to.
حتى أنك ستشرب الغسول إذا اضطررت لذلك.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
My memory is amazing.
ذاكرتي مذهلة.
The people who bought me jade flooring or lent me money.
الأشخاص الذين اشتروا لي أرضيات اليشم أو أقرضوني المال.
I still remember all their phone numbers.
لا أزال أتذكر جميع أرقام هواتفهم.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
And I know you have phone chargers.
وأنا أعلم أن لديك شواحن الهاتف.
Your phone's at 100%, right?
هاتفك مشحون بنسبة 100%، أليس كذلك؟
Don't think I'm that easy to fool.
لا أعتقد أنني من السهل خداعي.
I'll be right back.
سأعود حالا.
Ugh, this backwater town.
آه، هذه المدينة النائية.
Doubt there are any taxis here.
أشك في وجود أي سيارات أجرة هنا.
Hey! Wait!
مهلا! انتظر!
Give me a ride!
أعطني رحلة!
- Excuse me? - Give me a ride!
- عذرا؟ - أعطني رحلة!
Sure, get in.
بالتأكيد، ادخل.
Don't you have a phone charger?
هل ليس لديك شاحن للهاتف؟
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Did you know my daughter already?
هل تعرفت على ابنتي بالفعل؟
I first met her when she came to the kindergarten.
لقد التقيت بها لأول مرة عندما جاءت إلى روضة الأطفال.
My cousin is the principal here.
ابن عمي هو المدير هنا.
What do you do?
ماذا تفعل؟
Me?
أنا؟
I'm a farmer.
أنا مزارع.
Farmers are wealthier these days, you know.
المزارعون أصبحوا أكثر ثراءً هذه الأيام، كما تعلمون.
You must own some land.
يجب أن تمتلك بعض الأراضي.
I rent land to grow strawberries.
أستأجر أرضًا لزراعة الفراولة.
Pfft.
بفت.
All show and no substance.
كل هذا عرض ولا يوجد أي مضمون.
Where's the kid's mother?
أين أم الطفل؟
I'm raising him alone.
أنا أربيته وحدي.
How young were you when you messed up? You don't look the type.
كم كان عمرك عندما أخطأت؟ لا يبدو عليك هذا النوع من الأشخاص.
Your parents?
والديك؟
Died in an accident.
توفي في حادث.
Without parents, what would a child have to learn from?
بدون الوالدين ماذا يتعلم الطفل من؟
Did you also grow up without a mother, without anyone to look up to, old lady?
هل نشأت أيضًا بدون أم، بدون أي شخص تتطلع إليه، يا سيدتي العجوز؟
What? You little brat.
ماذا؟ أيها الطفل الصغير.
Ju Won, don't talk back to adults.
جو وون، لا تتحدث مع الكبار.
Hey, how old are you?
مهلا، كم عمرك؟
And why are you calling me old lady?
ولماذا تناديني بالسيدة العجوز؟
You cheeky little thing.
أنت شيء صغير وقح.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
What do you think this is?
ما رأيك في هذا؟
She has investigated all of us.
لقد قامت بالتحقيق معنا جميعا.
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
Professor Ga.
البروفيسور جا.
What is this about?
ما هذا؟
There's an extraordinary general meeting next week, right?
هناك اجتماع عام استثنائي في الأسبوع المقبل، أليس كذلك؟
The matter of dismissing Vice President Ga Seon Woo and electing a new CEO.
مسألة إقالة نائب الرئيس جا سون وو وانتخاب رئيس تنفيذي جديد.
Please postpone the Seon Woo issue,
من فضلك تأجيل قضية سون وو،
and I'd like to be recommended as the CEO.
وأود أن يتم ترشيحي كرئيس تنفيذي.
Today's meeting is sort of a request.
إن اجتماع اليوم هو نوع من الطلب.
Since I'm the one making the request,
بما أنني أنا من قدم الطلب،
it looks like you guys are 'the ones in power'
يبدو أنكم أنتم "أصحاب السلطة"
and I'm 'the one at your mercy'.
وأنا "الذي تحت رحمتك".
'The ones in power' and 'the one at your mercy'.
'الذين في السلطة' و 'الذين تحت رحمتك'.
Then what's with that behind you?
إذن ما الأمر مع ذلك خلفك؟
Professor Ga?
البروفيسور جا؟
Though I'm asking for a favor, I don't want to be pathetic.
على الرغم من أنني أطلب معروفًا، إلا أنني لا أريد أن أكون مثيرًا للشفقة.
Pathetic?
مثير للشفقة؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Dad.
أب.
Su... Su Jin.
إنهم... إنهم يسمعون.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Professor Ga, what are you doing?
أستاذ جا، ماذا تفعل؟
Still, blood is thicker than water.
ومع ذلك، فإن الدم أكثر سمكا من الماء.
Wait...
انتظر...
Director Kim.
المخرج كيم.
Yes?
نعم؟
If you spent company money on erectile dysfunction medication to enjoy yourself,
إذا أنفقت أموال الشركة على أدوية علاج ضعف الانتصاب من أجل الاستمتاع،
now your daughter has to pay for it with her body.
الآن يجب على ابنتك أن تدفع ثمن ذلك بجسدها.
Eyes, kidneys, liver, all in perfect condition.
العيون والكلى والكبد كلها في حالة ممتازة.
And her organs are pristine.
وأعضائها سليمة.
You raised her well.
لقد ربيتها جيدا.
She'll fetch a high price.
سوف تحصل على سعر مرتفع.
Professor Ga.
البروفيسور جا.
- I'll do anything. - Dad.
- سأفعل أي شيء. - أبي.
Please just forgive me this once.
من فضلك فقط سامحيني هذه المرة.
Director Han.
المخرج هان.
Yes.
نعم.
Your son's face looks very swollen.
يبدو أن وجه ابنك منتفخًا جدًا.
I was wrong.
لقد كنت مخطئا.
Professor Ga, I'm sorry.
أستاذ جا، أنا آسف.
Only my son...
فقط ابني...
- My son... - I'll do anything you ask.
- ابني... - سأفعل أي شيء تطلبه.
Please, spare my son...
من فضلك، أنقذ ابني.
[Loyalty Pledge]
[تعهد الولاء]
Directors.
المخرجين.
I've always been the one in power, so I'm not used to being on the receiving end.
لقد كنت دائمًا صاحب السلطة، لذلك لست معتادًا على أن أكون في الجانب المتلقي.
People should wear clothes that suit their position, right?
ينبغي على الناس أن يرتدوا ملابس تتناسب مع مكانتهم، أليس كذلك؟
Stamp the document.
ختم الوثيقة.
- Yes.
- نعم.
We confirmed Vice President Ga Seon Woo is at Cheongmu Psychiatric Hospital.
لقد تأكدنا أن نائب الرئيس جا سون وو موجود في مستشفى تشونغمو للأمراض النفسية.
Bring him to me immediately.
أحضره لي على الفور.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Sir.
سيد.
Please, save me.
من فضلك أنقذني.
Hey.
يا.
Call Lee Don for me.
اتصل بي لى دون.
Call Attorney Lee for me.
اتصل بالمحامي لي من أجلي.
Yes.
نعم.
I'll be right there.
سأكون هناك حالا.
Yes, amidst the winds of change, there were hardships,
نعم، وسط رياح التغيير، كانت هناك صعوبات،
economic indicators are gradually showing signs of recovery, offering positive signals.
وتظهر المؤشرات الاقتصادية تدريجيا علامات التعافي، مما يوفر إشارات إيجابية.
Having endured the crisis, we can now look forward to better days ahead.
وبعد أن تجاوزنا هذه الأزمة، أصبح بإمكاننا الآن أن نتطلع إلى أيام أفضل قادمة.
That concludes today's news report.
وهذا يختتم تقريرنا الإخباري اليوم.
- This has been GNA News. - What?
- هذه هي أخبار وكالة الأنباء الوطنية. - ماذا؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Why isn't it airing?
لماذا لا يتم بثه؟
Senior.
كبير.
What happened to my piece?
ماذا حدث لقطعتي؟
The corruption piece on Gaseong Group's board members.
قطعة الفساد حول أعضاء مجلس إدارة مجموعة غاسونغ.
It got blocked from above.
لقد تم حظره من الأعلى.
Ga Seon Yeong said she doesn't need it anymore.
قالت جا سون يونغ أنها لم تعد بحاجة إليه.
Your source was Ga Seon Yeong, right?
مصدرك كان جا سون يونغ، أليس كذلك؟
Jeez, that's absurd.
يا إلهي، هذا سخيف.
Pyo Seung Hee, you need more reporter instincts.
بيو سونغ هي، أنت بحاجة إلى المزيد من غرائز المراسل.
Can't you see the obvious?
ألا تستطيع رؤية الواضح؟
They used you to recruit the board members.
لقد استخدموك لتجنيد أعضاء مجلس الإدارة.
To the conglomerates like them, reporters like us are just pawns.
بالنسبة للشركات الكبرى مثلهم، فإن الصحفيين مثلنا هم مجرد بيادق.
Senior.
كبير.
I'll dig into every corner of Ga Seon Yeong's life now. Don't stop me.
سأبحث في كل جانب من جوانب حياة غا سيون يونغ الآن. لا توقفوني.
Okay, keep digging and get that scoop.
حسنًا، استمر في الحفر واحصل على تلك المعلومة.
Where is he?
أين هو؟
We can't disclose patient information.
لا يمكننا الكشف عن معلومات المريض.
Speak now.
تكلم الآن.
[Administration Office]
[مكتب الإدارة]
You have the proof, right?
لديك الدليل، أليس كذلك؟
How many times? I've told you already, I'm telling you.
كم مرة؟ لقد أخبرتك بالفعل، وأنا أخبرك.
How can I trust you?
كيف يمكنني أن أثق بك؟
Darn it, have you been fooled all this time?
يا لعنة، هل تم خداعك كل هذا الوقت؟
Attorney.
محامي.
Ga Seon Yeong sent men here.
أرسل جا سون يونغ رجالاً إلى هنا.
Vice President.
نائب الرئيس.
Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
الموقع الرسمي: kissasian.be ترجمة =Qari= @Team Viki
I'll trust that statement.
سأثق بهذا البيان.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
We have no time. Hurry up.
ليس لدينا وقت. أسرع.
Hey, it's him!
مهلا، إنه هو!
Over there.
هناك.
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
[Cheongmu Psychiatric Hospital]
[مستشفى تشونغمو للأمراض النفسية]
There are clothes in the back. Change into those.
هناك ملابس في الخلف. ارتدِها.
Okay.
تمام.
What type of guy do you like, Hye Ji?
ما هو نوع الرجل الذي يعجبك، هيه جي؟
A rough style like a general?
أسلوب خشن مثل الجنرال؟
Or a sweet, baby-faced look that makes you want to bite?
أم مظهر لطيف يشبه وجه الطفل ويجعلك ترغب في العض؟
Hye Ji, can I ask one thing?
هيه جي، هل يمكنني أن أسألك شيئًا واحدًا؟
I don't want to talk now.
لا أريد التحدث الآن.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Just one question.
سؤال واحد فقط .
Hye Ji, what type of guy do you...
هيه جي، ما نوع الرجل الذي...
Aren't you scared of my possessed state?
ألا تخاف من حالتي الممسوسة؟
Most people avoid me if they know.
معظم الناس يتجنبونني إذا عرفوا.
Ghosts aren't scary.
الأشباح ليست مخيفة.
Living people terrify me more.
الناس الأحياء يرعبونني أكثر.
Satisfied?
راضي؟
I answered you.
لقد أجبتك.
Buy me flowers next time.
اشتري لي الزهور في المرة القادمة.
I really like roses.
أنا حقا أحب الورود.
Okay.
تمام.
- Dong Min. - Huh?
- دونغ مين. - هاه؟
What does it mean when a woman asks for flowers?
ماذا يعني عندما تطلب المرأة الزهور؟
Ask your general.
اسأل الجنرال الخاص بك.
The general wouldn't know. He's single.
الجنرال لا يعرف، فهو أعزب.
Hey, the general's listening and getting angry.
مهلا، الجنرال يستمع ويغضب.
When a woman wants flowers, maybe...
عندما تريد المرأة الزهور، ربما...
Doesn't it mean she wants to be loved?
ألا يعني هذا أنها تريد أن تكون محبوبة؟
I love you, Jeon Dong Min.
انا احبك، جون دونج مين.
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
Hey, we need to fix the greenhouse door. Get ready quickly.
مهلا، علينا إصلاح باب الدفيئة. استعدوا بسرعة.
She wants to be loved.
إنها تريد أن تكون محبوبة.
That's Seo Hyeon's.
هذا هو سيو هيون.
[Muchang Supermarket]
[سوبر ماركت موتشانغ]
Now, it's my turn.
الآن جاء دوري.
[Psychopath]
[مختل عقليا]
No idea what could be my cash cow.
ليس لدي أي فكرة عما يمكن أن يكون بقرة نقدية بلدي.
I'll take care of what you told me to do soon.
سأعتني بما قلت لي أن أفعله قريبًا.
I'll do it myself.
سأفعل ذلك بنفسي.
It turned around.
لقد استدار.
Yes! I won!
نعم لقد فزت!
The penalty is writing names with your butt, right?
العقوبة هي كتابة الأسماء بمؤخرتك، أليس كذلك؟
- Yes. - I'll do it.
- نعم. - سأفعل ذلك.
Okay.
تمام.
Huh? Ju Won.
هاه؟ جو وون.
I'm going to the bathroom.
سأذهب إلى الحمام.
Okay.
تمام.
Oh? Me too.
أوه؟ وأنا أيضا.
Seo Hyeon, let's go together.
سيو هيون، دعنا نذهب معًا.
- Sure. - Yeah.
- بالتأكيد. - نعم.
Oh?
أوه؟
A little more this way.
أكثر قليلا بهذه الطريقة.
- Try matching it. - This is the spot.
- حاول مطابقته. - هذا هو المكان.
Wait, you can't let go now.
انتظر، لا يمكنك تركه الآن.
Yes, noon a.
نعم، ظهراً.
What?
ماذا؟
Ju Won disappeared?
هل اختفى جو وون؟
What? Ju Won? Oh, no.
ماذا؟ جو وون؟ أوه، لا.
Yeah, got it.
نعم حصلت عليه.
Yes.
نعم.
Jeong Hwa, what's going on?
جونغ هوا، ماذا يحدث؟
Oh, Jeong Woo, what do we do?
أوه، جونغ وو، ماذا نفعل؟
- What? Why? - Ju... Ju Won's missing.
- ماذا؟ لماذا؟ - جو... جو وون مفقود.
Ju Won? Why?
جو وون؟ لماذا؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
- Hey, you know Ju Won? - Yes.
- مهلا، هل تعرف جو وون؟ - نعم.
Hey, search every corner of this neighborhood.
مهلا، ابحث في كل زاوية من هذا الحي.
Don't worry, Jeong Hwa, okay?
لا تقلق يا جونغ هوا، حسنًا؟
I'll look for him.
سأبحث عنه.
Lee Jun's mom.
والدة لي جون.
This afternoon around 3 PM,
اليوم بعد الظهر حوالي الساعة 3 مساءًا،
Jeon Ju Won, son of villager Jeon Dong Min
جون جو وون، ابن القروي جون دونج مين
disappeared in front of Muchang Supermarket.
اختفى أمام سوبر ماركت موتشانج.
If anyone has Jeon Ju Won under their care,
إذا كان أي شخص لديه جون جو وون تحت رعايته،
please contact his worried father immediately.
يرجى الاتصال بوالده القلق على الفور.
Repeating the announcement.
تكرار الإعلان
This afternoon around 3 PM,
اليوم بعد الظهر حوالي الساعة 3 مساءًا،
Jeon Ju Won, son of Jeon Dong Min, disappeared near Muchang Supermarket.
جون جو وون، ابن جون دونج مين، اختفى بالقرب من سوبر ماركت موتشانج.
If anyone has Jeon Ju Won under their care,
إذا كان أي شخص لديه جون جو وون تحت رعايته،
please contact his worried father immediately.
يرجى الاتصال بوالده القلق على الفور.
Ju Won.
إنهم أفضل.
- Tae Min. - Yeah.
- تاي مين. - نعم.
- Not here? - Nope, not here either.
- ليس هنا؟ - لا، ليس هنا أيضًا.
Hey, check that side.
مهلا، تحقق من هذا الجانب.
I'll check this way.
سأتحقق من هذا الطريق.
Ju Won!
ارميهم!
What on earth is she doing?
ماذا تفعل على الأرض؟
Ju Won.
إنهم أفضل.
[Muchang Supermarket]
[سوبر ماركت موتشانغ]
32...
32...
Yeong Ran.
يونغ ران.
This supermarket is so crappy.
هذا السوبر ماركت سيء للغاية.
Even if I have money, there's nothing to buy.
حتى لو كان لدي المال، ليس هناك ما أشتريه.
Mom, did you really go alone?
أمي هل ذهبتِ وحدكِ حقاً؟
Why are you talking about all of a sudden?
لماذا تتحدث فجأة؟
Did you really go alone?
هل ذهبت وحدك حقا؟
Are you yelling at me now?
هل تصرخ علي الآن؟
Do you think I kidnapped some kid?
هل تعتقد أنني اختطفت طفلاً ما؟
You're misunderstanding me.
أنت تسيء فهمي.
This place obviously has nothing. Why take a kid?
من الواضح أن هذا المكان لا يوجد فيه شيء. لماذا تأخذ طفلاً؟
If anything happens to Ju Won, I won't forgive you.
إذا حدث أي شيء لجو وون، فلن أسامحك.
Understand?
يفهم؟
Whoa! Amazing.
واو! مذهل.
Is that kid more important than your own mom?
هل هذا الطفل أكثر أهمية من أمك؟
Ugh, disrespectful brat.
آه، طفل غير محترم.
Ju Won.
إنهم أفضل.
- Yes. - Ju Won might've gotten into some man's car.
- نعم. - ربما دخل جو وون في سيارة رجل ما.
My mom saw it while leaving the supermarket.
لقد رأته أمي عندما خرجت من السوبر ماركت.
Did you happen to get the license plate number?
هل حصلت على رقم لوحة الترخيص؟
Ah, no, not that part...
اه، لا، ليس هذا الجزء...
Understood.
مفهومة.
[Bus Stop]
[موقف الحافلات]
You'll miss your Mom, hurry.
سوف تفتقد والدتك، اسرع.
Yes, thank you.
نعم شكرا لك.
Okay.
تمام.
Mom!
أم!
Ju Won.
إنهم أفضل.
Ju Won!
ارميهم!
Jeon Ju Won!
جون جو وون!
Mom!
أم!
Mom, where are you?
أمي أين أنت؟
Mom.
أم.
Huh?
هاه؟
Mom!
أم!
Ju Won.
إنهم أفضل.
Ju Won!
ارميهم!
Hey, kid!
مهلا يا طفل!
You can't just jump out like that!
لا يمكنك القفز هكذا!
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
هل تحاول أن تقتل نفسك؟
Sorry, so sorry.
عذرا، عذرا جدا.
Ju Won, are you okay?
جو وون، هل أنت بخير؟
Yes.
نعم.
Miss, I missed Mom.
آنسة، لقد افتقدت أمي.
I think Mom came to see me.
أعتقد أن أمي جاءت لرؤيتي.
Huh?
هاه؟
Because I didn't recognize her,
لأنني لم أتعرف عليها،
I think she just left.
أعتقد أنها غادرت للتو.
No.
لا.
It's not your fault, Ju Won.
إنه ليس خطؤك، جو وون.
It's not your fault. It's okay, Ju Won.
ليس خطأك. لا بأس يا جو وون.
Jeon Ju Won!
جون جو وون!
Miss, are you okay?
آنسة هل أنت بخير؟
I'm okay.
انا بخير.
I think Ju Won was really scared.
أعتقد أن جو وون كان خائفًا حقًا.
What happened to you?
ما حدث لك؟
How did you end up here? I was so worried!
كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟ كنت قلقًا جدًا!
Dad, I'm sorry.
أبي، أنا آسف.
She looked like Mom.
لقد كانت تشبه أمي.
She really looked like Mom, Dad.
إنها حقا تشبه أمي وأبي.
I'm sorry, Dad.
انا آسف يا أبي.
No, Ju Won.
لا، جو وون.
I'm the one who's sorry.
أنا من آسف.
I didn't understand how you felt.
لم أفهم كيف شعرت.
I'm sorry for getting angry.
أنا آسف لأنني غضبت.
[Bus Terminal]
[محطة الحافلات]
Oh, and.
أوه، و.
I brought this from the hospital.
لقد أحضرت هذا من المستشفى.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Are you sure
هل أنت متأكد
the evidence is at home?
الدليل موجود في المنزل؟
Yes, it's right.
نعم إنه صحيح.
Just go home quickly.
فقط اذهب إلى المنزل بسرعة.
Hey, Lee Don.
مرحبًا، لي دون.
I need to use the restroom...
أحتاج إلى استخدام الحمام...
My stomach hurts. I need to go.
معدتي تؤلمني. أريد أن أذهب.
How much would you like to fill up?
كم تريد أن تملأ؟
Fill it up, please.
املأها من فضلك.
Okay.
تمام.
[Men's Restroom]
[حمام الرجال]
Who do you think I am?
من تعتقد أنني؟
50,000 won.
50,000 وون.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
Oh my, hey!
أوه يا إلهي!
Hey! You scammer.
مهلا! أيها المحتال.
Come back, you punk!
عد أيها الأحمق!
Lee Don, you idiot.
لي دون، أيها الأحمق.
I'm Ga Seon Woo!
أنا جا سون وو!
Ugh, that guy.
آه، ذلك الرجل.
Hey, you scammer.
مهلا، أيها المحتال.
You're in on his side too, huh?
أنت في صفه أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
I'm not a scammer, I'm a lawyer!
أنا لست محتالًا، أنا محامي!
I'll give you the money.
سأعطيك المال.
Oh, and... Could you call a taxi?
أوه، و... هل يمكنك استدعاء سيارة أجرة؟
Jeez.
جيز.
Did I go too far?
هل ذهبت بعيدا جدا؟
Yes, there's a damaged vehicle here.
نعم، هناك سيارة متضررة هنا.
Oh, this place...
أوه، هذا المكان...
Ga Seon Woo?
ماذا عن سون وو؟
Lee Don, you punk.
لي دون، أيها البانك.
You think I don't know your scheme?
هل تعتقد أنني لا أعرف خطتك؟
You think I'll die twice from the same trick?
هل تعتقد أنني سأموت مرتين من نفس الخدعة؟
I predicted you'd run away, VP.
لقد توقعت أنك ستهرب، نائب الرئيس.
I'm a lawyer who charges 10,000 won per minute.
أنا محامي أتقاضى 10000 وون في الدقيقة.
Did you dare look down on me?
هل تجرأت على النظر إلي؟
Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
الموقع الرسمي: kissasian.be ترجمة =Qari= @Team Viki
I'll kill everyone, my sister and all.
سأقتل الجميع، أختي وكل شيء.
- You're here. What happened? - Jeong Woo.
- أنت هنا. ماذا حدث؟ - جونغ وو.
They found Ju Won.
لقد وجدوا جو وون.
Sis, they found him.
أختي لقد وجدوه.
Jeong Hwa, you okay? Lean on me.
جونغ هوا، هل أنتِ بخير؟ اتّكئي عليّ.
Hey, Kang Seong Tae.
مرحبًا، كانغ سيونغ تاي.
Aren't you going home?
ألن تذهب إلى المنزل؟
Me?
أنا؟
Why? I'm gonna have some ramyeon.
لماذا؟ سأتناول بعض الراميون.
Hey, Jeong Hwa.
مرحبًا، جونغ هوا.
Since they found Ju Won, get some rest.
بما أنهم وجدوا جو وون، احصلوا على بعض الراحة.
I'll come help close up shop later.
سآتي لمساعدتك في إغلاق المتجر لاحقًا.
Oh, thanks.
اوه، شكرا.
Take a rest.
خذ قسطا من الراحة.
Miss, are you okay?
آنسة هل أنت بخير؟
I can go home and get some medicine...
أستطيع أن أذهب إلى المنزل وأحصل على بعض الأدوية...
Ah, it's okay.
اه، لا بأس.
I have some emergency medicine too.
لدي بعض الأدوية الطارئة أيضًا.
Thank you for saving Ju Won.
شكرا لك على إنقاذ جو وون.
But don't rush at the car like that.
ولكن لا تتسرع في السيارة هكذا.
You're not made of steel.
أنت لست مصنوعًا من الفولاذ.
What I'm saying is
ما أقوله هو
please think about yourself first.
من فضلك فكر في نفسك أولا.
Okay.
تمام.
But are you angry?
ولكن هل انت غاضب؟
No, it's just...
لا، إنه فقط...
Yes, I'm angry.
نعم أنا غاضب.
Then take this.
ثم خذ هذا.
It's candy for when you're angry.
إنها حلوى عندما تكون غاضبًا.
Anyway, you're really unpredictable.
على أية حال، أنت حقا لا يمكن التنبؤ بها.
Miss!
يفتقد!
Dad, I'll take her home.
أبي، سآخذها إلى المنزل.
Yeah, make sure you take her home.
نعم، تأكد من أنك تأخذها إلى المنزل.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go, Miss.
دعنا نذهب يا آنسة.
I'm fine though.
أنا بخير رغم ذلك.
Ju Won.
إنهم أفضل.
Can I ask you something?
هل يمكننى ان اسألك شيئا؟
Did you follow someone earlier?
هل تابعت شخصًا في وقت سابق؟
Well
حسنًا
actually.
في الحقيقة.
I went alone.
ذهبت وحدي.
She really looked like my mom,
إنها حقا تشبه أمي،
so I followed her.
لذلك اتبعتها.
Dad must've been really upset because of me earlier, right?
يبدو أن أبي كان منزعجًا جدًا بسببي في وقت سابق، أليس كذلك؟
No.
لا.
Ju Won, you really missed your mom, didn't you?
جو وون، لقد افتقدت والدتك حقًا، أليس كذلك؟
Dad says Mom's studying in France,
يقول الأب أن أمي تدرس في فرنسا،
but I know that's not true.
ولكنني أعلم أن هذا ليس صحيحا.
The neighborhood ladies said Mom abandoned me and left.
قالت سيدات الحي أن أمي تخلت عني ورحلت.
I really hate my mom.
أنا أكره أمي حقًا.
I don't like that lady either.
أنا لا أحب هذه السيدة أيضًا.
Ju Won.
إنهم أفضل.
I don't have a dad.
ليس لدي أب.
But, you have
ولكن لديك
an amazing dad
أب رائع
who loves only you.
من يحبك فقط
I really envy that.
أنا حقا أحسد ذلك.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
My dad's the best.
والدي هو الأفضل.
He's truly wonderful, right?
إنه رائع حقًا، أليس كذلك؟
Miss, I'm leaving now.
آنسة، أنا ذاهب الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
Goodnight.
طاب مساؤك.
Sleep well.
نم جيداً.
You too, Miss.
و أنت أيضا يا آنسة.
[Sujeong Hotel]
[فندق سوجيونغ]
[Ms. Bu Se Mi]
[السيدة بو سي مي]
Madam.
سيدتي.
It seems that the situation might be resolved easily.
ويبدو أن الوضع قد يتم حله بسهولة.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Ga Seon Woo has something significant.
لدى جا سون وو شيئًا مهمًا.
If we secure that, your exile will end.
إذا حصلنا على ذلك، فإن نفيك سينتهي.
Mom came to Muchang.
أمي جاءت إلى موتشانج.
Ah, so she went there.
اه، لذلك ذهبت إلى هناك.
Attorney Lee, what do you mean by that?
المحامي لي، ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
You knew all along and didn't contact me?
لقد كنت تعرف طوال الوقت ولم تتواصل معي؟
Kim So Yeong isn't important right now, madam.
كيم سو يونغ ليست مهمة الآن، سيدتي.
Don't forget
لا تنسى
how much this game is worth.
كم تساوي هذه اللعبة؟
Where did he throw it?
أين رماها؟
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
It's been a while.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
I contacted you because I need a favor.
لقد اتصلت بك لأنني أحتاج إلى خدمة.
[20-19, Eumjeon-ro 28beon-gil, Muchang-my eon, Muchang County, Gyeongnam]
[20-19، Eumjeon-ro 28beon-gil، Muchang-my eon، مقاطعة Muchang، Gyeongnam]
[Professor, I'll handle it soon]
[أستاذ، سأتعامل مع الأمر قريبًا]
♫ Starting to be born again ♫
♫ البدء في الولادة من جديد ♫
♫ Now is the time ♫
♫ الآن هو الوقت ♫
I want to look into the background of someone who previously worked here.
أريد أن أبحث في خلفية شخص عمل هنا سابقًا.
Seon Woo, where are you right now?
سون وو، أين أنت الآن؟
Again, again, again!
مرة أخرى، مرة أخرى، مرة أخرى!
Sis, don't you remember that day?
أختي، ألا تتذكرين ذلك اليوم؟
I'll just send this to Kim Yeong Ran.
سأرسل هذا إلى كيم يونج ران.
We might end this game quickly without bloodshed.
ربما ننهي هذه اللعبة بسرعة دون إراقة دماء.
She changed her identity?
هل غيرت هويتها؟
If Kim Yeong Ran dies now, it'll complicate things.
إذا مات كيم يونج ران الآن، فإن الأمور سوف تتعقد.
Why did you follow me last night?
لماذا تبعتني الليلة الماضية؟
Are you spying on me?
هل تتجسس علي؟
Then if that woman dies instead of Kim Yeong Ran...
ثم إذا ماتت تلك المرأة بدلاً من كيم يونج ران...
Maybe it wouldn't be such a bad thing for someone else to die.
ربما لن يكون الأمر سيئًا جدًا أن يموت شخص آخر.